[
  {
    "Question": "Joey played Dr. Drake Ramoray on which soap opera show?",
    "Answer": "Days of Our Live."
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many times did Ross get divorced?",
    "Answer": "Three."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What store does Phoebe hate?",
    "Answer": "Pottery Barn."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rachel got a job with which company in Paris?",
    "Answer": "Louis Vuitton."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are the names of Ross and Monica's parents?",
    "Answer": "Jack and Judy Geller."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the occupation of Rachel's fiancé Barry Farber?",
    "Answer": "Orthodontist."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Phoebe's scientist boyfriend David worked in what city?",
    "Answer": "Minsk."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Monica dated an ophthalmologist named?",
    "Answer": "Richard."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which <strong>Sprouse</strong> brother played Ross' son Ben?",
    "Answer": "Cole."
  },
  {
    "Question": "True or false, Rachel kissed all of her Friends (male and female) on the show?",
    "Answer": "True."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Chandler Bing's middle name?",
    "Answer": "Muriel."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who pees on Monica after she is stung by a jellyfish?",
    "Answer": "Chandler."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of Phoebe's twin sister?",
    "Answer": "Ursula."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ross says whose name at the altar in London?",
    "Answer": "Rachel."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which member of the British royal family appeared on Friends</em>?",
    "Answer": "Sarah Ferguson/Duchess of York."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Brad Pitt and David Schwimmer's characters cofounded what club in high school?",
    "Answer": "The I Hate Rachel Green Club."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of Joey's sisters did Chandler fool around with?",
    "Answer": "Mary Angela."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who was Joey's imaginary childhood friend?&nbsp;",
    "Answer": "Maurice."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the profession of Joey's imaginary friend?",
    "Answer": "Space cowboy."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was Monica's nickname when she was a field hockey goalie?",
    "Answer": "Big Fat Goalie."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does Rachel guess Chandler's job is?",
    "Answer": "A transponster."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Richard's daughter's name?",
    "Answer": "Michelle."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is Joey's agent?",
    "Answer": "Estelle."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who&nbsp;mistakingly&nbsp;threw a woman's wooden leg into a fire?",
    "Answer": "Joey."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the name of Chandler and Ross' college band?",
    "Answer": "Way, No Way."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Monica categorizes her towels into how many categories?",
    "Answer": "11."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ross and Rachel's wedding dinner was held where in Vegas?",
    "Answer": "A Pizza Hut."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Joey and Chandler's TV guide is addressed to who?",
    "Answer": "Miss Chanandler Bong."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the name of Ross' pet monkey?",
    "Answer": "Marcel."
  },
  {
    "Question": "According to Monica, a woman has how many erogenous zones?",
    "Answer": "Seven."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does Phoebe legally change her name to after her wedding?",
    "Answer": "Princess Consulea Banana Hammock."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What form of self-defense does Ross try to teach Rachel and Phoebe?",
    "Answer": "Unagi."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What song makes Ross and Rachel's daughter Emma laugh for the first time?",
    "Answer": "Sir Mix-a-Lot's Baby Got Back."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of Joey's stuffed penguin?",
    "Answer": "Hugsy."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What caused the fire at Rachel and Phoebe's apartment?",
    "Answer": "Rachel's hair straightener."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Phoebe is a surrogate for who?",
    "Answer": "Her half-brother Frank Jr. and his wife Alice."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What color is Monica's apartment?",
    "Answer": "Purple."
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many sisters does Joey have?",
    "Answer": "Seven."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Joey doesn't share what?",
    "Answer": "Food."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of Chandler's father's Las Vegas all-male burlesque?",
    "Answer": "Viva Las Gaygas."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Phoebe attempts to teach Joey what language?",
    "Answer": "French."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Chick Jr. and Duck Jr. got stuck in what?",
    "Answer": "A foosball table."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who was married to a supposedly gay Canadian ice dancer named Duncan?",
    "Answer": "Phoebe."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rachel was in which sorority?",
    "Answer": "Kappa Kappa Delta."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are the names of Rachel's sisters?",
    "Answer": "Jill and Amy Greene."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which character famously said, PIVOT?",
    "Answer": "Ross."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Phoebe finds what in her soda can?",
    "Answer": "A human thumb."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who was (accidentally) Monica's first kiss?",
    "Answer": "Her brother Ross."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rachel goes on Ross' honeymoon by herself where?",
    "Answer": "Athens, Greece."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What holiday does Chandler hate?",
    "Answer": "Thanksgiving."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who was Rachel's prom date?",
    "Answer": "Chip Matthews."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the name of Ross and Monica's dog when they were kids?",
    "Answer": "Chi-Chi."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What actor played Phoebe's husband Mike Hannigan?",
    "Answer": "Paul Rudd."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where did Ross and Rachel have their first date?",
    "Answer": "The planetarium."
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many roses did Ross send Emily?",
    "Answer": "72."
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many pages was Rachel's letter to Ross?",
    "Answer": "Eighteen pages (front and back)."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What year did Friends first premiere?",
    "Answer": "1994."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Joey's Cabbage Patch Kid is named what?",
    "Answer": "Alicia May Emory"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the name of the game Chandler made up to give Joey money?",
    "Answer": "Cups."
  },
  {
    "Question": "In an effort to get over Richard, Monica started making what?",
    "Answer": "Jam."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What fruit is Ross allergic to?",
    "Answer": "Kiwi."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Rachel's favorite flower?",
    "Answer": "Lillies."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the name of Ross and Rachel's male nanny?",
    "Answer": "Sandy."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who came on to who in The One With The Videotape?",
    "Answer": "Rachel came on to Ross."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was Joey's nickname when he was working at Alessandro's?",
    "Answer": "Dragon."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Monica worked as a waitress at what diner?",
    "Answer": "Moondance Diner."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was Rachel's bra size?",
    "Answer": "32C."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ross worked as a professor at what school?",
    "Answer": "New York University."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What word did Rachel misspell on her resume?",
    "Answer": "Computer."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are the names of the triplets Phoebe gives birth to?",
    "Answer": "Frank Jr. Jr., Leslie and Chandler."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who said, See, he's her lobster!",
    "Answer": "Phoebe."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What city is Friends</em> set in?",
    "Answer": "New York City."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first wedding gift Monica opens?",
    "Answer": "A tiny salt shaker."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rachel's sister Amy decides she wants to become what after babysitting Emma?",
    "Answer": "A baby stylist."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ross and Carol were busted having sex on which Disney ride?",
    "Answer": "It's a Small World."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Friend entered a Vanilla Ice lookalike contest and won?",
    "Answer": "Chandler."
  },
  {
    "Question": "True or false, Monica ate macaroni off a jewelry box she made.",
    "Answer": "True."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What ingredient did Rachel&nbsp;mistakingly&nbsp;put in her Thanksgiving trifle?",
    "Answer": "Beef."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Phoebe thought Kenny the Copy Guy was who?",
    "Answer": "Ralph Lauren."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who dated a college student named Elizabeth Stevens?",
    "Answer": "Ross."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Monica could not tell time until what age?",
    "Answer": "13."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Phoebe created a three-dimensional picture of a woman named?",
    "Answer": "Gladys."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who was the last Friend to find out about Monica and Chandler's relationship?",
    "Answer": "Ross."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Chandler and Joey both dated an actress named?",
    "Answer": "Kathy."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What did Monica want from Phoebe as an engagement present?",
    "Answer": "Her grandmother's cookie recipe."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who had a pony and a boat at age 15?",
    "Answer": "Rachel."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Phoebe said something was wrong with the right or the left phalange of Rachel's plane?",
    "Answer": "The left."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is Santa's friend that Ross invents to teach Ben about Hanukkah?",
    "Answer": "The Holiday Armadillo."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is the youngest Friend?",
    "Answer": "Rachel."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Chandler told Janice he was moving where to avoid seeing her again?",
    "Answer": "Yemen."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who introduced Phoebe and Mike?",
    "Answer": "Joey."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Phoebe's grandmother said she got her cookie recipe from her grandmother named?",
    "Answer": "Nestle Toulouse (AKA Nestlé Toll House)."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Joey's stalker Erika Ford was played by which actress?",
    "Answer": "Brooke Shields."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who did Monica forget to invite to Rachel's baby shower?",
    "Answer": "Rachel's mother Sandra."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of Monica's boyfriends wanted to become the Ultimate Fighting Champion?",
    "Answer": "Pete (Peter Becker)."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the name of the lipstick brand for men that Joey starred in a Japanese commercial for?",
    "Answer": "Ichiban."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ross, Susan and Phoebe got stuck where before Ben's birth?",
    "Answer": "A closet."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who gave Phoebe away at her wedding?",
    "Answer": "Chandler."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Monica and Chandler first got together where?",
    "Answer": "London."
  },
  {
    "Question": "The handcuffs that were found in Rachel's former room belonged to who?",
    "Answer": "Monica and Ross' Nana (grandmother)."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Chandler and Ross helped Joey practice for what game show audition?",
    "Answer": "Bamboozled."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does Chandler call the Paris of Oklahoma?",
    "Answer": "Tulsa."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What food caused Ross to get sick on Space Mountain?",
    "Answer": "Tacos."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is older Ross or Monica?",
    "Answer": "Ross."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is actually</em> Rachel's favorite movie?",
    "Answer": "Weekend at Bernie's</em>."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Friend had a traumatic swing incident at age 4?",
    "Answer": "Rachel."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ross and Rachel's daughter Emma would have turned 18 what year?",
    "Answer": "2020."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Friend didn't go to London for Ross' wedding?",
    "Answer": "Phoebe."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What kind of bed did the Mattress King deliver to Monica?",
    "Answer": "A racecar bed."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Emma's first birthday cake was supposed to be shaped like what?",
    "Answer": "A bunny."
  },
  {
    "Question": "In what part of her body did Monica get a pencil stuck at age 14?",
    "Answer": "Her ear."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ross created a comic book called what?",
    "Answer": "Science Boy</em>."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Joey's favorite food?",
    "Answer": "Sandwiches."
  },
  {
    "Question": "How old was Chandler when he first touched a girl's breast?",
    "Answer": "19."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Monica's biggest pet peeve?",
    "Answer": "Animals dressed as humans."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Friend had his/her identity stolen?",
    "Answer": "Monica."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Joey&nbsp;doesn't read which book without making sure there is plenty of room in the&nbsp;freezer?",
    "Answer": "The Shining</em>."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of Ross and Monica's maternal grandmother?",
    "Answer": "Althea."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who stole all the insoles out of Chandler's shoes?",
    "Answer": "Chandler's roomate Eddie."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who gave Rachel and Ross the name Emma for their daughter?",
    "Answer": "Monica."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Joey was cast as the butt double for which actor?",
    "Answer": "Al Pacino."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of Phoebe's alter ego?",
    "Answer": "Regina Phalange."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What year did the series finale of Friends</em> air?",
    "Answer": "2004."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the name of Rachel and Monica's building superintendent?",
    "Answer": "Mr. Treeger."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Joey's pin number?",
    "Answer": "5639."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the last state that Ross couldn't&nbsp;remember?",
    "Answer": "Delaware."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the name of Chandler's roommate prior to Joey?",
    "Answer": "Kip."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Whose idea was it to get married in Vegas, Rachel or Ross'?",
    "Answer": "Rachel."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the name of Monica's imaginary boyfriend?",
    "Answer": "Jared."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What kind of plastic surgery did Rachel have?",
    "Answer": "A nose job."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who was called Sir Limps-a-Lot after losing a toe?",
    "Answer": "Chandler."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the name of Rachel's hairless cat?",
    "Answer": "Mrs. Whiskerson."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which balloon got away during the Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade in Season 1?",
    "Answer": "Underdog."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who gave birth to Chandler and Monica's twins?",
    "Answer": "Erica."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Chandler and Rachel ate cheesecake off the floor from what bakery? &nbsp;",
    "Answer": "Mama's Little Bakery."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Friend once mugged Ross?",
    "Answer": "Phoebe."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Monica, Ross and Rachel attended what high school?",
    "Answer": "Lincoln High School."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who were on a break?",
    "Answer": "Rachel and Ross."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ross was jealous of who at Rachel's job?",
    "Answer": "Mark."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the name of the hot girl from the Xerox place?",
    "Answer": "Chloe."
  },
  {
    "Question": "What did Rachel get a tattoo of?",
    "Answer": "A heart."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is the first Friend to speak on the show?",
    "Answer": "Monica."
  }
]
